<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Gone with the Rimwave (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.GonewiththeRimwave</packageId>
  <author>Fierydraken</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/GonewiththeRimwave</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies />
  <loadAfter />
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]
Update of Fierydrakens mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1342263292

[img]https://i.imgur.com/pufA0kM.png[/img]

[table]
	[tr]
		[td][url=https://invite.gg/Mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
		[td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/GonewiththeRimwave][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/WjDSfUn.png[/img][/td]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/6KqTKks.png[/img][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Z4GOv8H.png[/img]

The mod is based on the comic "Gone with the blastwave".
http://www.blastwave-comic.com/index.php?p=comic&amp;nro=1


This mod adds the Red Army, Blue Army, Yellow Army, and their weapons into Rimworld.

The uniforms: Provides some armour and a little bit of heat insolation
The helmets: Provides armour and toxic fallout protection
(Yellow's gear is more powerful)

Wasteland Rifle: Box standard survival weapon used by the Reds and the Blues.
Wireframe Wasteland Rifle: The standard rifle, but with a wireframe stock. Has a accuracy and range penalty.
Advanced Wasteland Rifle: Used by the Yellows, it is a superior version of the standard rifle.
Wasteland LMG: A heavy gun used by the Reds and the Blues.
Wasteland Flamer: Its a flamethrower, what more could you want? (May be OP)


Q/A
Q: What about the greens, I am angry and upset you have not added them!
A: The greens got too close to a centipede and have died. I have added their uniforms and helmets.

Q: Will you add the 250k and/or Legends versions?
A: currently I have no plans to.

Q: Will you add other non lore friendly armys?
A: Nope.

Q: Can I craft these items?
A: You can craft all of the items at their appropriate benches.


███████████████████████████
███████▀▀▀░░░░░░░▀▀▀███████
████▀░░░░░░░░░░░░░░░░░▀████
███│░░░░░░░░░░░░░░░░░░░│███
██▌│░░░░░░░░░░░░░░░░░░░│▐██
██░└┐░░░░░░░░░░░░░░░░░┌┘░██
██░░└┐░░░░░░░░░░░░░░░┌┘░░██
██░░┌┘▄▄▄▄▄░░░░░▄▄▄▄▄└┐░░██
██▌░│██████▌░░░▐██████│░▐██
███░│▐███▀▀░░▄░░▀▀███▌│░███
██▀─┘░░░░░░░▐█▌░░░░░░░└─▀██
██▄░░░▄▄▄▓░░▀█▀░░▓▄▄▄░░░▄██
████▄─┘██▌░░░░░░░▐██└─▄████
█████░░▐█─┬┬┬┬┬┬┬─█▌░░█████
████▌░░░▀┬┼┼┼┼┼┼┼┬▀░░░▐████
█████▄░░░└┴┴┴┴┴┴┴┘░░░▄█████
███████▄░░░░░░░░░░░▄███████
██████████▄▄▄▄▄▄▄██████████
███████████████████████████

------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
This is my first mod and would not have been possible without my prolific poultry protege, Chicken Plucker. He is seriously just about the coolist and most helpful person I have met online.
A big thanks to DARK for the art for the guns.

[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[/list]

</description>
</ModMetaData>